11130 Stratford Drive Apt 403 OKC, OK 73120

To Whom It May Concern:

I am writing about any open positions that are currently available with your company. My educational background and experience as a writer, editor and social media strategist have provided me with the skills needed to excel in various positions.

I am Lawrence Evans, but I am simply known as Lance. I am a graduate of Hampton University with a BA in print journalism and a minor in English. Throughout my career as a writer, I have had the opportunity to work with various local publications including the *Oklahoma Gazette*, *Oklahoma Family Metro Magazine*, *Outlook* and *Slice Magazine* as well as national media outlets like *Gather News*. Although my articles for these publications helped fuel my passion for writing, it was my volunteer work with *Citizens Caring for Children*—a local nonprofit organization—that truly helped me realize the power of words and the impact that they can have when used through social media.

In addition, my position as a Social Media Director for *Search King* and as a Social Media Strategist for *APMEX* allowed me to find new and interesting ways to engage followers of mainstream media. Furthermore, my most recent position as a Research and Writing Specialist and Public Assistance Liaison for the *Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA)* uses all my skills to provide aid to survivors impacted by the severe storms, tornadoes, straight-line winds and flooding in Oklahoma on May 18-June 2.

My educational background and experience demonstrate my ability to be an effective worker. I have attached a copy of my resume for more detail on my skills and qualifications. For more information or to schedule a meeting, I can be reached at (405) 250-4752 or by e-mail at lawrence.h.evans@gmail.com.

or to schedule a meeting, I can be reached at (403) 230-4732 or by e-mail at	
lawrence.h.evans@gmail.com.	
Thoule your for your against and and the state of the sta	

Thank you for your consideration.

Sincerely,

Lawrence Evans

Lawrence H. Evans

Lawrence.h.evans@gmail.com 11130 Stratford Drive Apt 403 OKC, OK 73120 405.250.4752

Education

Hampton University Hampton, VA Major: Print Journalism Minor: English Graduation: May 2007 GPA: 3.7/4.1

Experience

Research and Writing Specialist

07/2013-present

Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), Oklahoma City, OK

- Write news releases, media advisories, social media posts and other content for External Affairs Department.
- Public Assistance Liaison—keep survivors updated with latest information on funding.

Contributing Writer 01/2013-present

Outlook, Edmond, OK

- Write cover stories on impacting issues in Edmond and OKC.
- Edit materials and conduct interviews for print content.

Social Media Strategist 04/2012-07/2013

APMEX, Oklahoma City, OK

- Connected with customers on Facebook, Twitter, Yelp and other social media platforms.
- Wrote weekly blogs on the precious metals industry and company policy.

Contributing Writer 03/2012-present

Oklahoma Gazette, Oklahoma City, OK

- Write feature articles on entertainment news, fashion and events.
- Conduct interviews for online and print content.

Social Media Strategist/Marketing Committee Member 03/2012-present

Citizens Caring for Children, Oklahoma City, OK

- Maintain Facebook, Twitter, and other social media sites for organization.
- Help organize various events as member of marketing team.

Contributing Writer 10/2011-02/2013

Slice, Oklahoma City, OK

- Conducted interviews for publication.
- Wrote articles covering stories impacting OKC Metro area.

Contributing Writer 07/2011-09/2011

The Edmond Sun, Edmond, OK

- Wrote for companion magazine *The Business Times of Edmond*.
- Conducted interviews for source material.

Social Media Director 06/2010-05/2011

Search King, Oklahoma City, OK

- Maintained blogs and social media accounts for clients.
- Conducted research using various social media tools for companies.

References

Amy Mitchell, Executive Director

Citizens Caring for Children, OKC, OK

(405) 753-4099

Jenn Scott, Lifestyles Editor

Oklahoma Gazette, OKC, OK

(405) 589-0158

Bethany Scott, Print Project Manager

Outlook Magazine, Edmond, OK
(405) 341-5599 ext 1018

Lindsay Laird, Vice President
Saxum, OKC, OK
(405) 605-2003

Lawrence H. Evans

Lawrence.h.evans@gmail.com 11130 Stratford Drive Apt 403 OKC, OK 73120 405.250.4752

Education

Hampton University Hampton, VA Major: Print Journalism Minor: English Graduation: May 2007 GPA: 3.7/4.1

Experience

Researcher/Writer 07/2013-present

 $\textit{Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA)}, Oklahoma\ City, OK$

- Write news releases, media advisories, blogs and social media content for External Affairs Department.
- Public Assistance Laison—keep survivors impacted by tornadoes on May 18-June2 with latest grant info.

Contributing Writer 01/2013-present

Outlook, Edmond, OK

- Write cover stories on impacting issues in Edmond and OKC.
- Edit materials and conduct interviews for print content.

Social Media Strategist 04/2012-07/2013

APMEX, OKC, OK

- Connect with customers on Facebook, Twitter, Yelp and other social platforms.
- Write weekly blogs on the precious metals industry and company policy.

Contributing Writer 03/2012-present

Oklahoma Gazette, Oklahoma City, OK

- Write feature articles on entertainment news, fashion and events.
- Conduct interviews for online and print content.

Social Media Strategist/Marketing Committee Member

Citizens Caring for Children, Oklahoma City, OK

- Maintain Facebook, Twitter, and other social media sites for organization.
- Help organize various events as member of marketing team.

Contributing Writer 10/2011-02/2013

03/2012-present

Slice, Oklahoma City, OK

- Conducted interviews for publication.
- Wrote articles covering stories impacting OKC Metro area.

Contributing Writer 07/2011-09/2011

The Edmond Sun, Edmond, OK

- Wrote for companion magazine *The Business Times of Edmond*.
- Conducted interviews for source material.

Social Media Director 06/2010-05/2011

Search King, Oklahoma City, OK

- Maintained blogs and social media accounts for clients.
- Conducted research using various social media tools for companies.

References

Amy Mitchell, Executive Director Jenn Scott, Lifestyles Editor Citizens Caring for Children, OKC, OK Oklahoma Gazette, OKC, OK

(405) 753-4099 (405) 589-0158

Bethany Scott, Print Project Manager

Outlook Magazine, Edmond,

(405) 341-5599 ext 1018

Lindsay Laird, Vice President

OK Saxum, OKC, OK

(405) 605-2003